RESUME



EDUCATION

Kuban State University, Krasnodar

2017-2021

Postgraduate diploma

"Computer Science and Computer Engineering"

2015-2017

Master's degree (diploma with honors)

"Applied Mathematics and Computer Science"

2011-2015

Bachelor

"Mathematical support and administration of information systems"

COURCES

Certificates of completion of the courses of the ANOO "International School of Banking Business":

"Documenting a computer network at various stages of its life cycle";

"Information security in banks";

"Computer hardware. Information storage devices":

"Network equipment";

"Technical means of informatization.

Information output devices";

"Technical means of informatization. Information input devices"

SKILLS

Golang

PHP

Python (Scrapy, Tkinter, XML, JSON, MySQL)

JS (Ajax, jQuery, d3.js), CSS, HTML

C#, C++

Vitaly Gudza

Golang Developer (Russia, Krasnodar / remote)

Email to contact: vitalg93 https://github.com/vitalg93

ABOUT

I am 27 years old, my programming experience is more than 10 years, of which I worked in the team as a Chief Technical Officer of a startup for 3 years. During this time, I wrote code in C++, C#, Delphi, Python, Assembler, Java, PHP, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3 and worked with MySQL. Now I am studying Golang and I am looking for a team in which I can realize my potential of specialized education in the field of information technology and mathematics. I learn quickly. I write code efficiently. I understand business processes and methods of their optimization. The priority in the work is the *development of user-friendly and user-oriented software*.

WORK EXPERIENCE

OKT 2019 - SEP 2021

Junior Researcher

Kuban State University, Krasnodar

Conducting scientific research with the help of mathematical simulations in the Comsol Multiphysics calculation program. More than 25 scientific articles have been published, 5 certificates of state registration of computer programs have been obtained, the results have been publicly presented at more than 15 scientific conferences

OKT 2016 - DEC 2019

сто

Artificial Intelligence Laboratory, Krasnodar

Web development:

Fullstack development of an adaptive sports social network website (PHP+UIKit/JS) - profile, feed page, settings, etc. Automation of email newsletters, user awards for completing challenges (Cron), generation of PDF certificates for challenge winners. Special attention was paid to the performance and security of the code. Implementation of the author's secure system for storing transactions (awards) of users based on the modification of the Blockchain. Using the Vkontakte API for authorization/registration on the site and the Google Maps API.

Application programming:

Development of central modules of a prototype of a general AI (chatbot) in Python 3. Design of the project architecture and the functionality of methods in accordance with the task statement. Development of Unit tests. Optimization of complex AI algorithms for low productive hardware (Raspberry Pi 4).

Data science:

Parsing of open web resources, processing of Big Data for training an Al system. Mobile development:

Independent development and publication in Google Play of an Android application (web view) for displaying the mobile version of the social network being developed. Enabling Push notifications using Firebase Cloud Messaging.

Administration:

Installation, configuration and administration of the Ubuntu Server. Installation and configuration on the GitLab server and software for organizing Samba Server file sharing. *Additionally:*

Hiring, training, adaptation and management of a group of programmers, conducting code-review, working with Git. Presentation of development results at IT conferences and competitions, participation in IT conferences (KRD DEV days). Development of a set of company programming rules based on PEP8. Victory with colleagues in the start-up competition from the "IIDF" (VC FUND AND ACCELERATOR) – Krasnodar, Russia (2017)

Languages spoken: Russian (native speaker) English technical (B2)